Records, 1972-1984 related records, 1971-1978
Smithsonian Institution Archives
Records
1972-1984 related records, 1971-1978
Smithsonian Institution Archives, Washington, D.C., osiaref@si.edu
Smithsonian Institution, Office of the Under Secretary
SI Records
23 linear meters.
Record Unit 392
Historical Note
The Office of the Under Secretary was created in 1973, and the incumbent reported directly to the Secretary of the Institution and acted as his principal advisor. The first Under Secretary was Robert A. Brooks, who served until his death in 1976. Michael Collins served as the second Under Secretary from 1978 to 1980 and was succeeded by Phillip S. Hughes, 1980-.
Descriptive Entry
These records document the Under Secretary's involvement in all aspects of the Institution's operations from the perspective of a senior policy-maker, as well as contacts with governmental, corporate, and private bodies with which the Smithsonian interacted as it conducted its affairs. A few records deal with Brooks's work as Deputy Under Secretary and Assistant Secretary and with Collins's directorship of the National Air and Space Museum.
Index Terms
This collection is indexed under the following access terms. These are links to collections with related topics, persons or places.
Name
Collins, Michael, 1930-; Brooks, Robert Angus, 1920-; Hughes, Phillip S., 1917-; Smithsonian Institution -- Administration.
- OFFICE OF THE UNDER SECRETARY, RECORDS, 1972-1975., Series 1
  - Box 1
    - Agenda Working Group, 1972 (Box 1 of 23)
    - Agenda Working Group, old (Box 1 of 23)
    - Announcements, old (Box 1 of 23)
    - BMD (Buildings Management Department), 1973 (2 folders) (Box 1 of 23)
    - Budget (Box 1 of 23)
    - Bureau Directors Minutes, 1972-1973 (Box 1 of 23)
    - Executive Committee, 1972 (Box 1 of 23)
    - Registrarial Council, 1972-1973 (Box 1 of 23)
    - Commons Operations (Box 1 of 23)
    - Cooper-Hewitt (Box 1 of 23)
    - Computer Service Study Plan, 1974 (Box 1 of 23)
    - Council of Directors, 1972-1973 (Box 1 of 23)
    - Energy Conservation Conference (Box 1 of 23)
    - Executive Committee, 1973 (Box 1 of 23)
    - Child Care and Women Council, 1973 (Box 1 of 23)
    - Exhibits, 1972 (Box 1 of 23)
    - Executive Development, 1972-1973 (Box 1 of 23)
    - International Relations (Box 1 of 23)
    - Management Survey, Chesapeake Bay Center, 1974 (Box 1 of 23)
    - Office of Development, 1973 (Box 1 of 23)
    - Issuance of Directives-Pending (Box 1 of 23)
    - SI Directives Issuance System (Box 1 of 23)
    - Libraries, 1973-1974 (Box 1 of 23)
    - SI Press and Pubs., 7-1-1972 thru 12-31-1972 (Box 1 of 23)
    - SI Press and Pubs., 1-1972 thru 6-30-1972 (Box 1 of 23)
  - Box 2
    - Office of Plant Services (OPlants) Review: Status of OM-771 (Box 2 of 23)
    - OPlants Review: Revision OM-771 (Box 2 of 23)
    - OPlants Review: Relamping #2 (Box 2 of 23)
    - OPlants Review: Relamping #1 (Box 2 of 23)
    - OPlants Review: Final Report (Box 2 of 23)
    - OPlants Review: Current/Mtgs (Box 2 of 23)
    - OPlants Review: 2nd Draft-Final Rpt (Box 2 of 23)
    - OPlants Review: 1st Draft-Final Rpt (Box 2 of 23)
    - OPlants Review: General Background (Box 2 of 23)
    - OPlants Review: Workflow (Box 2 of 23)
    - OPlants Review: OPlants Background (Box 2 of 23)
    - Computer Study: Final Report (Box 2 of 23)
    - Computer Study: Comments, Final Report (Box 2 of 23)
    - Computer Study: Final Report, Outline/Drafts (Box 2 of 23)
    - Computer Study: Preliminaries (Box 2 of 23)
    - Computer Study: Drafts-Finals Rpt (Box 2 of 23)
    - Computer Study: Dartmouth Computer Center (Box 2 of 23)
    - Computer Study: Admin. Applications (Box 2 of 23)
    - Computer Study: Collections Management, Applications (Box 2 of 23)
    - Computer Study: Research Applications (Box 2 of 23)
    - Computer Study: User Interviews (Box 2 of 23)
    - Computer Study: Usage Report (Box 2 of 23)
    - Computer Study: Usage Report: Background Materials (Box 2 of 23)
    - Computer Study: Computer Ctr Histories (Box 2 of 23)
    - Computer Study: Computer History Background Materials (Box 2 of 23)
    - Computer Study: Meeting Summaries (Box 2 of 23)
    - Computer Study: Computer History Background Materials (Box 2 of 23)
    - Computer Study: Summary of Computer Centers (Box 2 of 23)
    - Computer Study: Interviews (Box 2 of 23)
    - Computer Study: ISD ADP (Automatic Data Processing) 5 year Plan (Box 2 of 23)
    - Computer Study: Selgem (Self-Generating Master) (Box 2 of 23)
    - Computer Study: GSA (General Services Administration) ADP Regulations (Box 2 of 23)
    - Computer Study: Background Articles (Box 2 of 23)
    - Computer Study: Senate of Scientists Report-ADP (Box 2 of 23)
    - Computer Study: Ad Hoc Panel Rpt (Box 2 of 23)
    - Computer Study: ISD-Background Materials (Box 2 of 23)
- OFFICE OF THE UNDER SECRETARY, RECORDS, 1972-1974., Series 2
  - Box 3
    - Administrative Officers Council, CY 1974 (Box 3 of 23)
    - Anacostia Neighborhood Museum, CY 1974 (Box 3 of 23)
    - Anthropological Film Archive, 1973-1974 (Box 3 of 23)
    - Architectural Records Offices, American, 1-12/1973 (Box 3 of 23)
    - Arts and Industries Building, CY 1974 (Box 3 of 23)
    - Arts and Industries Building, 1-12/1973 (Box 3 of 23)
    - Assistant Secretary, Office of the, 1-12/1973 (Box 3 of 23)
    - Associates, Smithsonian Society of, CY 1974 (Box 3 of 23)
    - Audits, Office of, CY 1974 (Box 3 of 23)
    - Bicentennial of American Revolution, CY 1974 (Box 3 of 23)
    - Buildings Management Department, 1-12/1973 (Box 3 of 23)
    - Budget, FY 1974 (Box 3 of 23)
    - Budget, FY 1973 (Box 3 of 23)
    - Budget, 1973-1974 (Box 3 of 23)
    - Center for the Study of Man, 1973-1974 (Box 3 of 23)
    - Chesapeake Bay Center for Environmental Studies, CY 1974 (Box 3 of 23)
    - Commons, 1-12, 1973 (Box 3 of 23)
    - Contracts, 1973-1974 (Box 3 of 23)
    - Cooper-Hewitt Museum, CY 1974 (Box 3 of 23)
    - Development, Office of, CY 1974 (Box 3 of 23)
    - Elementary and Secondary Education, Office of, 1973-1974 (Box 3 of 23)
    - Equal Opportunity Office, CY 1974 (Box 3 of 23)
    - Executive Committee (Minutes), CY 1974 (Box 3 of 23)
    - Exhibits, CY 1974 (Box 3 of 23)
    - Facilities Planning and Engineering Services, CY 1974 (Box 3 of 23)
  - Box 4
    - Folklife Festival, CY 1974 (Box 4 of 23)
    - Fort Pierce Bureau, CY 1974 (Box 4 of 23)
    - Freer Gallery of Art, 1973-1974 (Box 4 of 23)
    - General Counsel, CY 1974 (Box 4 of 23)
    - General Services Administration, CY 1974 (Box 4 of 23)
    - Hillwood, CY 1974 (Box 4 of 23)
    - Hirshhorn Museum and Sculpture Garden, CY 1974 (Box 4 of 23)
    - Information System Division, 1-12/1973 and 1/1974 (Box 4 of 23)
    - Johnson, CY 1974 (Box 4 of 23)
    - Legislation, 1-12/1973 (Box 4 of 23)
    - Libraries, Smithsonian 1973-1974 (Box 4 of 23)
    - Mall, CY 1974 (Box 4 of 23)
    - Mall, Last Remaining Site, CY 1973-1974 (Box 4 of 23)
    - Management Analysis Office, CY 1974 (Box 4 of 23)
    - Monthly Program Report (Box 4 of 23)
    - Museum Programs, Office of, CY 1974 (Box 4 of 23)
    - Museum Shops, July 1972-1974 (Box 4 of 23)
    - Museum Support Facility, CY 1974 (Box 4 of 23)
    - National Air and Space Museum, CY 1974 (Box 4 of 23)
    - National Capital Planning Commission, 1973-1974 (Box 4 of 23)
    - National Collection of Fine Arts, CY 1974 (Box 4 of 23)
    - National Gallery of Art, 1-12/1973 (Box 4 of 23)
    - National Gallery of Art, CY 1974 (Box 4 of 23)
    - National Museum Act, 1973-1974 (Box 4 of 23)
    - National Museum of Natural History, CY 1974 (Box 4 of 23)
    - National Museum of History and Technology, CY 1974 (Box 4 of 23)
    - National Portrait Gallery, CY 1974 (Box 4 of 23)
  - Box 5
    - Office of Management and Budget, 1973-1974 (Box 5 of 23)
    - Parking (employee), CY 1974 (Box 5 of 23)
    - Parking-Mall, CY 1974 (Box 5 of 23)
    - Parking-Employee and Public, July-December, 1972 (Box 5 of 23)
    - Mall-Parking, July-December, 1972 (Box 5 of 23)
    - Parking, 1-12/1973 (Box 5 of 23)
    - Performing Arts, CY 1974 (Box 5 of 23)
    - Personnel, CY 1974 (Box 5 of 23)
    - Photographic Services, Division of, 1973-1974 (Box 5 of 23)
    - Plant Services, CY 1974 (Box 5 of 23)
    - Press, S. I., CY 1974 (Box 5 of 23)
    - Protection Services, CY 1974 (Box 5 of 23)
    - Public Affairs, CY 1974 (Box 5 of 23)
    - Publications Review Board, CY 1974 (Box 5 of 23)
    - Public Service, CY 1974 (Box 5 of 23)
    - Supply Division, CY 1974 (Box 5 of 23)
    - Special Events, CY 1974 (Box 5 of 23)
    - Smithsonian Tropical Research Institute, CY 1974 (Box 5 of 23)
    - Smithsonian Science Info. Exchange, CY 1974 (Box 5 of 23)
    - Smithsonian Institution Traveling Exhibition Service, 1973-1974 (Box 5 of 23)
    - SI Building, 1973-1974 (Box 5 of 23)
    - Smithsonian Institution, CY 1974 (Box 5 of 23)
    - Smithsonian Council, CY 1974 (Box 5 of 23)
    - Space Allocations, Jan.-Dec. 1973 (Box 5 of 23)
- OFFICE OF THE UNDER SECRETARY, RECORDS, 1978-1979, WITH RELATED RECORDS, 1971-1978., Series 3
  - Box 6
    - Treasurer, CY 1974 (Box 6 of 23)
    - Treasurer, 1-12/1973 (Box 6 of 23)
    - Yale University (Box 6 of 23)
    - Smithsonian Astrophysical Observatory, CY 1974 (Box 6 of 23)
    - Silver Hill (Box 6 of 23)
    - Seminars, Office of (Box 6 of 23)
    - Science, Assistant Secretary for, FY 1974 (Box 6 of 23)
    - Science, Assistant Secretary for (Box 6 of 23)
    - Renwick Gallery, 1-12/73 (Box 6 of 23)
    - Regional Museums-Aerospace Museums in the West, July-December 1972 (Box 6 of 23)
    - Regents, CY 1974 (Box 6 of 23)
    - Zoological Park, National, FY 1974 (Box 6 of 23)
  - Box 7
    - Invitations Speaking: Regretted (Box 7 of 23)
    - Invitations Speaking: Regretted 1977 (Box 7 of 23)
    - Invitations Speaking: Regretted 1974-1976 (Box 7 of 23)
    - Invitations Speaking: Regretted 1971-1973 (Box 7 of 23)
    - Biography (Box 7 of 23)
    - Appointment books, 1971-1979 (Box 7 of 23)
    - Admin (Box 7 of 23)
    - MC: Acting (Box 7 of 23)
    - A (Box 7 of 23)
    - MC: Smithsonian Admin (Box 7 of 23)
    - Senior Seminar (State Department) at NASM, Nov 5, 1976 (Box 7 of 23)
  - Box 8
    - Albatross Aircraft (Walter Adey) (Box 8 of 23)
    - Anacostia Museum (Box 8 of 23)
    - Appropriations, 1979 (Box 8 of 23)
    - Arts and Industries Building (Box 8 of 23)
    - SI Associates: RAP (Resident Associates Program)/NSF (National Science Foundation) Grant, 1978 (Box 8 of 23)
    - Associates (Box 8 of 23)
    - Astronauts (Box 8 of 23)
    - Audiovisual Programs (Box 8 of 23)
    - Audits (Box 8 of 23)
    - Audits-Peratino Memoranda (Box 8 of 23)
    - Audit, Investigative and Review Resources (Box 8 of 23)
    - Auxiliary Activities (Box 8 of 23)
    - Awards and Medals (Box 8 of 23)
    - B (Box 8 of 23)
    - Barro Colorado Island (Box 8 of 23)
    - Belmont (Box 8 of 23)
    - Hermann Bretsch (Box 8 of 23)
    - Brookings Institution Conference for Senior Government Executives (Box 8 of 23)
    - Robert A. Brooks Award (Box 8 of 23)
    - Budget-FY 1978 Supplemental (Box 8 of 23)
    - Budget-FY 1979 (Box 8 of 23)
    - Budget-FY 1980 (Box 8 of 23)
    - Budget-Zero Base 1980 (Box 8 of 23)
    - Burden, William A.M. (Box 8 of 23)
    - By-laws (Box 8 of 23)
    - Business Management Office (Box 8 of 23)
    - C (Box 8 of 23)
    - Chron-1978 (Box 8 of 23)
    - David Challinor (Box 8 of 23)
    - Chesapeake Bay Center (Box 8 of 23)
    - Background Paper for Chesapeake Bay Center for Environmental Studies) CBCES Review (5-31-1979) (Box 8 of 23)
    - China (Box 8 of 23)
    - CBCES Personnel Information (Box 8 of 23)
    - Civil Service Reform (Box 8 of 23)
    - Combined Federal Campaign (Box 8 of 23)
    - Commission of Fine Arts (Box 8 of 23)
    - Congress (Box 8 of 23)
    - Cooper-Hewitt Museum (Box 8 of 23)
    - Council of Directors (Box 8 of 23)
    - Council of Directors-MC Chairman (Box 8 of 23)
    - D (Box 8 of 23)
    - Development Office (Box 8 of 23)
    - Wilton Dillon-Seminars (Box 8 of 23)
    - Congressman John D. Dingell (Box 8 of 23)
    - Division of Performing Arts (Box 8 of 23)
    - E (Box 8 of 23)
  - Box 9
    - Endowment (Box 9 of 23)
    - Ethics in Government (Box 9 of 23)
    - Executive Committee 1979 (Box 9 of 23)
    - Executive Committee 1978 (Box 9 of 23)
    - Exposition Books (Jake Page) (Box 9 of 23)
    - Five Year Plans (Box 9 of 23)
    - F (Box 9 of 23)
    - FBI (Box 9 of 23)
    - Folklife (Box 9 of 23)
    - Freer (Box 9 of 23)
    - Front Royal (Box 9 of 23)
    - G (Box 9 of 23)
    - Senator Goldwater (Box 9 of 23)
    - Great Hall (Box 9 of 23)
    - H (Box 9 of 23)
    - Hirshhorn (Box 9 of 23)
    - National Museum of History and Technology (Box 9 of 23)
    - Horticulture (Box 9 of 23)
    - HUD (Housing and Urban Development) Report (Box 9 of 23)
    - Hughes Report (Box 9 of 23)
    - I (Box 9 of 23)
    - Inman Collection (Box 9 of 23)
    - International Affairs (Box 9 of 23)
    - J (Box 9 of 23)
    - Japanese-American Society (Box 9 of 23)
    - Erica Jong (Box 9 of 23)
    - K (Box 9 of 23)
    - Lee Kimche (Box 9 of 23)
    - L (Box 9 of 23)
    - Ben Lawless (Box 9 of 23)
    - Legal Office (Box 9 of 23)
    - Library (Box 9 of 23)
    - Lindbergh Memorial Fund (Box 9 of 23)
    - M (Box 9 of 23)
    - Magazine (Box 9 of 23)
    - Mailing Lists (Box 9 of 23)
    - Museum of African Art (Box 9 of 23)
    - MHT (Museum of History and Technology): Makovenyi Bretzfelder (Box 9 of 23)
    - Museum Support Center: 10/1979 (Box 9 of 23)
    - Museum Support Center: 9/1978 to 9/1979 (Box 9 of 23)
    - Museum Support Center: Smithsonian Institution (bound booklet) (Box 9 of 23)
    - Support Center (5/31/1979) (Box 9 of 23)
    - Environmental Impact Assessment: Suitland Federal Center (Box 9 of 23)
    - Mc (Box 9 of 23)
    - N (Box 9 of 23)
    - NASA (National Aeronautics and Space Administration) (Box 9 of 23)
    - National Air and Space Museum (NASM) (Box 9 of 23)
  - Box 10
    - NASM-Congressman Mineta's interest in John J. Montgomery (Box 10 of 23)
    - E. Richard Sorenson-National Anthropological Film Center, 1978-1980 (Box 10 of 23)
    - National Board of Associates (Box 10 of 23)
    - National Capital Planning Commission (Box 10 of 23)
    - National Endowment for the Humanities (Box 10 of 23)
    - National Museum Act (Box 10 of 23)
    - Museum of Natural History (Box 10 of 23)
    - NCFA (National Collection of Fine Arts) (Box 10 of 23)
    - NCFA/White House: Paintings (Box 10 of 23)
    - National Portrait Gallery (Box 10 of 23)
    - National Science Foundation (Box 10 of 23)
    - National Visitors Center (Box 10 of 23)
    - Nuclear Regulatory Commission (Box 10 of 23)
    - O (Box 10 of 23)
    - OEO (Office of Equal Opportunity) (Box 10 of 23)
    - Office of Facilities Planning and Engineering Services (OFPES) (Box 10 of 23)
    - Office of Management and Budget (Box 10 of 23)
    - Office of Personnel Management (Box 10 of 23)
    - P (Box 10 of 23)
    - Parking-Mall (Box 10 of 23)
    - Parking (Paid) (Box 10 of 23)
    - Pennsylvania Avenue Development Corporation (Box 10 of 23)
    - Pension Building (Box 10 of 23)
    - Paul Perrot (Box 10 of 23)
    - Personnel (Box 10 of 23)
    - Personnel: Applications (Box 10 of 23)
    - Personnel: Executive Resources Board (Box 10 of 23)
    - Personnel: Grievances (Box 10 of 23)
    - Personnel: Hiring Freeze 1979 (Box 10 of 23)
    - Personnel Task Force (Box 10 of 23)
    - Personnel: Trust Fund (Box 10 of 23)
    - Pope Visit (Box 10 of 23)
    - Program Report (Box 10 of 23)
    - Public Services (Box 10 of 23)
    - Survey of Audio-Visual Materials at the Smithsonian Institution (Box 10 of 23)
    - Publications (Box 10 of 23)
    - Q (Box 10 of 23)
    - South Quadrangle: April 1979- (Box 10 of 23)
    - South Quadrangle: August 1978/April 1979 (Box 10 of 23)
  - Box 11
    - R (Box 11 of 23)
    - Radiation Biology Laboratory (Box 11 of 23)
    - Reading Is Fundamental (Box 11 of 23)
    - Regents Representatives and SI Staff-Meetings (Box 11 of 23)
    - Research Awards Program (Box 11 of 23)
    - S. Dillon Ripley (Box 11 of 23)
    - Board of Regents (Box 11 of 23)
    - Regents: Audit and Review Committee (Box 11 of 23)
    - Regents Personnel Committee (Box 11 of 23)
    - Regents Executive Committee (Box 11 of 23)
    - The Regents Newsletter: March 1979 (Box 11 of 23)
    - S (Box 11 of 23)
    - Arthur Sackler (Box 11 of 23)
    - Security (Box 11 of 23)
    - Senate of Scientists (Box 11 of 23)
    - Senior Executive Service (Box 11 of 23)
    - Shops (Box 11 of 23)
    - Silver Hill (Box 11 of 23)
    - Sinai-Research (Box 11 of 23)
    - Slides (Box 11 of 23)
    - James Smithson Society (Box 11 of 23)
    - Smithsonian Astrophysical Observatory (Box 11 of 23)
    - SI Council (Box 11 of 23)
    - Smithsonian Exposition Books (Box 11 of 23)
    - Smithsonian Fellowship Program (Box 11 of 23)
    - SI Press (Box 11 of 23)
    - SSIE-Smithsonian Science Information Exchange (Box 11 of 23)
    - STRI-Smithsonian Tropical Research Institute (Box 11 of 23)
    - Smithsonian Year 1979 (Box 11 of 23)
    - Smithsonian Year 1978 (Box 11 of 23)
    - Special Events (Box 11 of 23)
    - Stuart Portraits of George and Martha Washington (Box 11 of 23)
    - T (Box 11 of 23)
    - Tariff Building (Box 11 of 23)
    - U (Box 11 of 23)
    - V (Box 11 of 23)
    - VIP Visits (Box 11 of 23)
    - Vehicle Management (Box 11 of 23)
    - Victorian Garden (Box 11 of 23)
    - Visitors Center (Box 11 of 23)
    - W (Box 11 of 23)
    - James E. Webb (Box 11 of 23)
    - Ames Wheeler (Box 11 of 23)
    - White House (Box 11 of 23)
    - Women's Committee (Box 11 of 23)
    - Woodrow Wilson Center (Box 11 of 23)
    - Y (Box 11 of 23)
    - Zoo (Box 11 of 23)
    - Lees-McRae College (Box 11 of 23)
- OFFICE OF THE UNDER SECRETARY, RECORDS, 1980-1981., Series 4
  - Box 12
    - A (miscellaneous) (1981/1980) (Box 12 of 23)
    - Accountability for Research Activities (1980) (Box 12 of 23)
    - Affirmative Action Plan for Handicapped (1980) (Box 12 of 23)
    - Anacostia Neighborhood Museum (1981/1980) (Box 12 of 23)
    - Anti-fraud and Waste in Government (1981) (Box 12 of 23)
    - Archeometry (1981) (Box 12 of 23)
    - Archives (1981) (Box 12 of 23)
    - Archives of American Art (1980) (Box 12 of 23)
    - Arts Industries Building (1981) (Box 12 of 23)
    - Audits (1981/1980) (Box 12 of 23)
    - Auxiliary Activities (1980) (Box 12 of 23)
    - Awards (1981) (Box 12 of 23)
    - B (miscellaneous) (1981/1980) (Box 12 of 23)
    - Belmont (1981) (Box 12 of 23)
    - Brooks Award (1981/1980) (Box 12 of 23)
    - Business Management Office (1981) (Box 12 of 23)
    - C (miscellaneous) (1981-1980) (Box 12 of 23)
    - Camp Simms Property (1980) (Box 12 of 23)
    - Career Awareness Program (1981) (Box 12 of 23)
    - Chesapeake Bay Center (1981) (Box 12 of 23)
    - China (1981/1980) (Box 12 of 23)
    - Collections Management (1981/1980) (Box 12 of 23)
    - Collections Management Inventory Terminology (1981) (Box 12 of 23)
    - Congress (1981/1980) (Box 12 of 23)
    - Conservation Analytical Lab (1981/1980) (Box 12 of 23)
    - Continuing Resolution (1981) (Box 12 of 23)
    - Contracts (1981) (Box 12 of 23)
    - Cooper-Hewitt (1981) (Box 12 of 23)
    - Council of Directors (1981) (Box 12 of 23)
    - D (miscellaneous) (1980) (Box 12 of 23)
    - Development Office (1981/1980) (Box 12 of 23)
    - E (miscellaneous) (1981-1980) (Box 12 of 23)
    - Egypt Today (1981) (Box 12 of 23)
    - Equal Opportunity Office (1981/1980) (Box 12 of 23)
    - Executive Committee Meetings (change in proceedings) (1980) (Box 12 of 23)
    - Executive Resources Board (1981/1980) (Box 12 of 23)
    - Exhibits (1981/1980) (Box 12 of 23)
    - F (miscellaneous) (1980) (Box 12 of 23)
    - Fellowships and Grants (1981/1980) (Box 12 of 23)
    - Fund Raising-Auxiliary (1980) (Box 12 of 23)
    - Ft. Pierce (1980) (Box 12 of 23)
    - Freer Gallery (1980) (Box 12 of 23)
    - Financial Disclosure Statement (1979) (Box 12 of 23)
    - Five Year Prospectus (1980) (Box 12 of 23)
    - Fo1k1ife Programs (1981) (Box 12 of 23)
    - Fulfillment Operation (1981) (Box 12 of 23)
    - G (miscellaneous) (1980) (Box 12 of 23)
    - General Counsel (1981/1980) (Box 12 of 23)
    - H (miscellaneous) (1980) (Box 12 of 23)
    - Richard Howland (1981/1980) (Box 12 of 23)
  - Box 13
    - Information Resource Management (1981) (Box 13 of 23)
    - Inman Paintings (1980) (Box 13 of 23)
    - International Year of Disabled Persons (1981) (Box 13 of 23)
    - Illchman Report (1981) (Box 13 of 23)
    - OM (Office Memorandum) on Internships (1981) (Box 13 of 23)
    - Library (1981/1980) (Box 13 of 23)
    - M (miscellaneous) (1980) (Box 13 of 23)
    - Management Analysis Office (1981) (Box 13 of 23)
    - Murray Property (1980) (Box 13 of 23)
    - Museum of African Art (1981/1980) (Box 13 of 23)
    - Museum of Man (1980) (Box 13 of 23)
    - National Science Foundation (1980) (Box 13 of 23)
    - Museum Support Center (1981/1980) (Box 13 of 23)
    - National Air and Space Museum (1981) (Box 13 of 23)
    - National Arboretum (1980) (Box 13 of 23)
    - National Archives (1980) (Box 13 of 23)
    - National Armed Forces Advisory Board (1980) and report to Regents from Board dated 1975 (Box 13 of 23)
    - National Capital Planning Commission (1981/1980) (Box 13 of 23)
    - National Human Studies Film Center (1981)-National Anthropological Film Center (1981/1980) (Box 13 of 23)
    - National Maritime Museum (1980) (Box 13 of 23)
    - National Museum Act (1980) (Box 13 of 23)
    - National Museum of American Art (1981/1980) (Box 13 of 23)
    - National Museum of American History (1981/1980) (Box 13 of 23)
    - National Museum of Natural History (1981/1980) (Box 13 of 23)
    - Native American Archives project (1981) (Box 13 of 23)
    - National Museum of Natural History: Evans Gallery (1981/1980) (Box 13 of 23)
    - North Capitol Street (1980) (Box 13 of 23)
    - Office of Management and Budget (1981/1980) (Box 13 of 23)
    - Office of Personnel Management (1981/1980) (Box 13 of 23)
    - P (miscellaneous) (1981/1980) (Box 13 of 23)
    - Paul Perrot (1981/1980) (Box 13 of 23)
    - Payroll Personnel System (1981) (Box 13 of 23)
    - Personnel (1981/80) (Box 13 of 23)
  - Box 14
    - Personnel: Applicants (1981/1980) (Box 14 of 23)
    - Personnel: Freeze (1981/1980) (Box 14 of 23)
    - Personnel: Grievances (1980) (Box 14 of 23)
    - Personnel: Merit Pay (1981/1980) (Box 14 of 23)
    - Personnel: Performance Appraisal System (1981/1980/1979) (Box 14 of 23)
    - Personnel: Excomm Performance Appraisal (1981) (Box 14 of 23)
    - Personnel: Excomm Performance Review (1980) (Box 14 of 23)
    - Protection (1981) (Box 14 of 23)
    - Public Affairs (1981/1980) (Box 14 of 23)
    - Public Service (1981/1980) (Box 14 of 23)
    - Quadrangle (1981/1980) (Box 14 of 23)
    - R (miscellaneous) (1981) (Box 14 of 23)
    - Research Institute on Immigration and Ethnic Studies (1982/1981) (Box 14 of 23)
    - Franklin D. Roosevelt Centennial (1981) (Box 14 of 23)
    - Schiffirn Report (1980-also report from 1970) (Box 14 of 23)
    - James Smithson Society (1981/1980) (Box 14 of 23)
    - Smithsonian Astrophysical Observatory (1981/1980) (Box 14 of 23)
    - Smithsonian Council (1981/1980) (Box 14 of 23)
    - Smithsonian Exposition Books (1981/1980) (Box 14 of 23)
    - Smithsonian Magazine (1981/1980) (Box 14 of 23)
    - Smithsonian Publishing Council (1979) (Box 14 of 23)
    - Smithsonian Science Information Exchange (1982/1981/1980) (Box 14 of 23)
    - Smithsonian Institution Traveling Exhibition Service (1981/1980) (Box 14 of 23)
    - Special Events (1981/1980) (Box 14 of 23)